netbiscuits.com 2013-06-12

# Privacy Policy

## Data Protection of Netbiscuits GmbH for Netbiscuits.com

Netbiscuits GmbH (hereinafter referred to as „Netbiscuits“) take the protection of personal data very seriously. We would like you to know when we store which data and how long we use them. As a company under private law we are subject to the stipulations of the Federal Data Protection Law (BDSG) and the German Media Services Treaty (MST). We have taken technical and organizational measures that will ensure that the data protection regulations are observed both by us and by external service providers commissioned by us.

### Registration of Personal Information

Personal data will be used according to your business relations with Netbiscuits. The manner of data processing depends on the detailed services you receive from Netbiscuits. Personal data is all information that can be used to establish your identity. This includes information such as your name, address or phone number. This does not apply to information that cannot be connected to your true identity (for example favorite Websites or number of users of a site).

### Non-personal Identifiable Information

In connection with your access, data is stored on our servers for security purposes that could possibly allow identification (e.g. IP address, date, time and pages viewed). No personally identifiable utilization is carried out. We reserve the right to statistically evaluate anonymised data sets.

We store IP addresses for a period of 28 days. These are stored for reasons of data security to ensure the stability and operational reliability of our system.

### Circulation of Personal Information to Third Parties

We will not pass on your personal information to third parties without your consent except if it is for reasons of services to be executed by Netbiscuits. If data should be passed on to service providers in connection with commissioned data processing, these providers are bound by the FDPL, by other statutory regulations and contractually by Netbiscuits' own data protection policy. If we are obliged to do so by the law or by a court ruling, we will pass your data on to authorities entitled to receive the information.

### Right to Information and Cancellation

You can ask for stored information at any time and you also have the right to ask for personal data to be deleted in the future. In both cases we ask you to please contact us by per E-Mail (info@netbiscuits.com) or by phone (Tel.: +49 631 68036-100).

### Use of Cookies

We place “cookies” (small files with configuration information) to collect information relating to customer trends and patterns and we use cookies to measure site usages and related information. No personal data is collected by the use of cookies. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies or to be informed as soon as cookies are sent.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

Due to the fast development of the Internet it may become necessary from time to time to make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site or software from Netbiscuits after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

### Questions, Suggestions and Comments

Please send any questions, suggestions or comments on the subject of data protection by E-Mail to Netbiscuits (info@netbiscuits.com).

Kaiserslautern, 12/06/2012
